我们先来完成第一个任务
Let's do the first task.
接下来我会将display方法的名字改为displayquantity
I'm going to change the name of the display method to displayquantity.
程序里会出现报错
Now this causes some errors in our app.
现在我滑上来可以看到一个错误提示无法解析方法display(int)
If I scroll up I see an error that says cannot resolve method display int.
这个和第二个任务相关
This is actually related to the second task,
第二个任务会涉及改变方法调用的一些内容
where we asked if you need to change the way that the method is called.
这里报错是肯定的  因为我们修改了方法的名称
The answer is yes, because when we change the name of the method,
我们需要修改它调用的方式
we need to change the way that it's called.
所以在increment方法里  我会将这里改为displayQuantity
So, in the increment method, I'm going to change this to say displayQuantity,
在decrement方法中
and then decrement method,
同样将方法名称修改为displayQuantity
I'm going to change this to say displayQuantity as well.
现在我们的程序里没有错误了
Now there's no more errors in our app and
那么我们可以保存  然后在设备上运行程序
I can save this and then run the app on the device.
程序运行正常
And the app works as expected.
从用户界面上看不到什么改动
There's no user visible change, but internally,
但是在我们的代码内部  我们修改了方法名称
in our code, we did change the method name.